So that probably cost me in the neighborhood of probably $50 million.
I'll tell you a quick story.
I had a competitor that ended up taking a bunch of my top testimonials that we kind
of converted to semi-employees because they were big evangelists back in the gym launch
days.
This guy was offering one-on-one coaching to help people out.
I never did that.
So they were cheaper.
They were doing one-on-one and they had some of my top customers becoming advocates.
My feathers got all ruffled and I was like, it's war time.
We got to go to the mattresses.
We got to really change the business up.
And so I did this big relaunch internally to my existing customer base.
I did this big value stack and I said, you're going to get all this extra stuff, not for
the same price you're paying me, but for less.
I took my existing recurring base and I reduced my revenue by $500,000 top line per month.
I increased my costs and I took my top line down by $6 million.
I then ended up selling that business, obviously, and the business never recovered that profit.
And so that probably cost me in the neighborhood of probably $50 million.
That competitor ended up killing that business because it wasn't fucking profitable.
I was the market leader and someone came in to undercut me and then I said, oh, I'll copy
the moron.
You will never go out of business focusing on the customer.
You just focus on the customer and you'll win.